After we have learned about the kestrels algorithm, now let's implement it and see.
We start by defining that void, this Castro's method that took into the two meter.
Two there a.
And crash type and gold, the graph maximum and maximum.
These are the length.
Of the of the dimensions and and and start, we start by making the cost and the distance the cost is
to the at a distance is one the FDA and predecessor with the same maximum maximum maximum value, which
is defined as than before.
OK, so.
Creating a and we create the visited man at rig count a valuable met them men minimum distance and then
next, not I and variables.
We start recreating the coast metrics since we are dealing with to the hourly, we need to use that
nested loop.
I and J, and we start checking for graph equal to zero, then cost equal to infinity.
We start updating all the values equal to infinite.
Otherwise we make the cost index in the graph index.
I and G No.
Four, I equal to zero I less than an hour plus plus we start by making this and updating the distance
and index are equal to cost at start at the index.
So this is the cost.
This is the cost of ad start, which is the start that we have and need to pass.
So if the first element that we have seen it in the first animation that a is the first and the element
and its cost to reach A is zero.
So the initial start is zero.
So we we pass here zero, which is the variable value of the stock.
If it is, do we best do?
So the start is being used here.
No.
And we use the predecessor at index equal to start and visit index equal to zero.
The distance at the start is equal to zero, then visit the start.
At then the start is equal to one and the count equal to one.
So
we start by checking while countless then and minus one.
The minimum distance is equal to Infinity says for checking the minimum distance if the minimum distance
at index is less than the minimum distance and it's not visited.
So this is the very important usage of a visit that I would check if we have visited this method, this
element or not.
So if we go from A to B and B and we have C here and see it connected to B.
If we have moved from A to B and now moved from A to C and C has C connected with B and connected with
the in order to not allow that graph to flow from sea to B again, we put B and mark it as a visit.
So this is the usage of physics.
In this case, we are collecting and we are comparing that to expressions.
If they are true here and true here, then when we continue otherwise it is not applicable.
We are checking if the distance is the minimum and we it does not the visit that the previous the hour
this element previously.
No, the minimum distance is updated to distance Appendix II and the next node equal to high.
Andrew TCEQ visited that index next, or no is equal to one no thought, oh equal to zero I less than
an and I plus plus a visit that is not if it is not visited, we use that checking here.
So please concentrate with me now we check for the visit that that then next note next note equal to
one, we check for eye equal to zero eyelids then and eye plus plus we start by checking if it does
not visit and if it is the minimum distance plus cost at the next note.
At Index I, this is the cost to the array.
Having the first and exact next note and the second index is I less than the distance at index I.
So you see guys, this is the trick behind the Dish Orchestra's algorithm.
Then said the distance equal to at the next, equal to the minimum distance, plus the cost.
This is the addition here.
We can add the addition to the cost with the minimum distance and predecessor at the next equal to the
next note and count plus plus now printing the distance.
It's very simple.
We are printing that Appendix II and we have made that look no.
Let's start by making this program works by making Intergraph at maximum maximum I and you and equal
to seven.
We start by filling that graph and creating the elements from zero to zero is equal to zero from zero
to one is equal to zero.
There is no connection between zero and zero.
There is no connection between zero and one.
Connection between zero and two is presented because one and the discourse is one, and the cost to
reach zero is zero.
OK, and so on.
This is that I want from you to try to draw this graph.
How it would be.
In the final result.
OK.
So please post the video and think about how, what, how we can draw this graph and what these represent.
OK, I'm waiting for your solutions.
We put you equal to zero and we called that method.
The Shastra, we passed the graph and you this would be finding them at shortest distance in the graph.
So this is the kestrels algorithm, and see, I want from you to draw the graph and put the way the
cost you're like from moving from here to here, from A to B or from one to two.
How what is the cost and what is the initial state of that element?
Okay.
So I'm I think your solution in the comments below.
If you need any help, I am ready.
So please don't hesitate.
Please don't be shy.
Ask your questions in the comments below, and I'm ready.
So let's move to that Java.